{
  "categories": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "Category1_Example1": [
        {
          "question": "example1",
          "Answer": "correct1"
        },
        {
          "question": "example2",
          "Answer": "correct2"
        },
        {
          "question": "example3",
          "Answer": "correct3"
        },
        {
          "question": "example4",
          "Answer": "correct4"
        },
        {
          "question": "example5",
          "Answer": "correct5"
        },
        {
          "question": "example6",
          "Answer": "correct6"
        },
        {
          "question": "example7",
          "Answer": "correct7"
        },
        {
          "question": "example8",
          "Answer": "correct8"
        },
        {
          "question": "example9",
          "Answer": "correct9"
        },
        {
          "question": "example10",
          "Answer": "correct10"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "Category2_Example2": [
        {
          "question": "example1",
          "Answer": "correct1"
        },
        {
          "question": "example2",
          "Answer": "correct2"
        },
        {
          "question": "example3",
          "Answer": "correct3"
        },
        {
          "question": "example4",
          "Answer": "correct4"
        },
        {
          "question": "example5",
          "Answer": "correct5"
        },
        {
          "question": "example6",
          "Answer": "correct6"
        },
        {
          "question": "example7",
          "Answer": "correct7"
        },
        {
          "question": "example8",
          "Answer": "correct8"
        },
        {
          "question": "example9",
          "Answer": "correct9"
        },
        {
          "question": "example10",
          "Answer": "correct10"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "Category3_Example3": [
        {
          "question": "example1",
          "Answer": "correct1"
        },
        {
          "question": "example2",
          "Answer": "correct2"
        },
        {
          "question": "example3",
          "Answer": "correct3"
        },
        {
          "question": "example4",
          "Answer": "correct4"
        },
        {
          "question": "example5",
          "Answer": "correct5"
        },
        {
          "question": "example6",
          "Answer": "correct6"
        },
        {
          "question": "example7",
          "Answer": "correct7"
        },
        {
          "question": "example8",
          "Answer": "correct8"
        },
        {
          "question": "example9",
          "Answer": "correct9"
        },
        {
          "question": "example10",
          "Answer": "correct10"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "Category4_Example4": [
        {
          "question": "example1",
          "Answer": "correct1"
        },
        {
          "question": "example2",
          "Answer": "correct2"
        },
        {
          "question": "example3",
          "Answer": "correct3"
        },
        {
          "question": "example4",
          "Answer": "correct4"
        },
        {
          "question": "example5",
          "Answer": "correct5"
        },
        {
          "question": "example6",
          "Answer": "correct6"
        },
        {
          "question": "example7",
          "Answer": "correct7"
        },
        {
          "question": "example8",
          "Answer": "correct8"
        },
        {
          "question": "example9",
          "Answer": "correct9"
        },
        {
          "question": "example10",
          "Answer": "correct10"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}

